my goon says you can go on and we'll
take this off ice back to my office plus
bonus these girls want a bonus though
they just told us mining guild scams are
off the menu you wouldn't continue to
continue hiding with your laptop in a
bag of groceries in got sand sacks
hoping that said jokingly leaving me to
hash tag wait and hope and see behind
seven proxies you ran all locally and I
know it's not you seen but party vans
are not the parties that you see in your
screen
old school kick it back to command comm
when you still believe your one day
might not live with your mom on your
Apple 2e typing peek and poke when you
first ix quick for deep and throat John
McCain please let me beat the hoped
marketing campaign scribbled with pen
stains gone off that cocaine crashing
that fast train in Spain and watching
them the fire sparks that was a theory
yo before I was a warrior sharp